drpeppertuition.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy | Dr Pepper Snapple Group

UPDATED AS OF: January 2018

This privacy policy ( **“Privacy Policy”** ) applies solely to information collected through those Company web sites, web pages, interactive features, applications, widgets, blogs, text numbers,  social networking sites and other Company online or wireless offerings, and their respective contents,  that post a link to this Privacy Policy, including those listed above, whether accessed via computer, mobile device or other technology ( **"Sites"** ). The Sites are offered by Dr Pepper/Seven Up, Inc., Mott’s LLP, Snapple Beverage Corp., Canada Dry Mott’s, Inc., Bai Brands LLC, and applicable Dr Pepper Snapple Group parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies, Sites developers and other promotional partners (collectively, “ **the Company,”  **or  **“we”,**   **“us”, “our”** ). Some of our other sites and/or programs may have their own, possibly different, policies that are posted on their own sites. We encourage you to review those policies when using those sites..

This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected through the Sites, how such information may be used and/or shared with others, how we safeguard it and how you may access and control its use in connection with our marketing communications and activities. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, because by using the Sites you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. In addition, please review our Terms of Use, which governs your use of the Sites and any content you submit to the Sites.

**QUICK GUIDE TO CONTENTS**  

  1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON OUR SITES
    * Information You Provide To Us
    * Information We Collect Automatically
  2. HOW WE USE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH OUR SITES
  3. SHARING OF INFORMATION
    * Third Parties Providing Services On Our Behalf and Affiliates
    * Your Agreement To Have Your Personal Information Shared
    * Business Transfers
    * Legal Disclosures
  4. INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES
  5. YOUR CHOICE AND ACCESS
  6. ADVERTISING/BEHAVIORAL TARGETING; HOW TO OPT-OUT
 
  7.  CHILDREN
  8. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION
  9. OTHER SITES
  10. CONSENT TO PROCESSING AND TRANSFER OF INFORMATION
  11. CHANGES
  12. CONTACT US

####    
1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON OUR SITES

**Information You Provide To Us**

The Sites may ask you to provide information that could reasonably be used to contact you or to identify you personally (such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, mobile phone number, or home address (" **Personal Information** ")). For example, we may collect Personal Information when you register on the Sites, request information, submit comments or participate in some promotion, survey or other feature of the Sites, or otherwise communicate or interact with us. The Sites may also ask you to provide other information about yourself, such as demographic information (gender, zip code, age, etc.) or certain information about your preferences and interests. If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it.

**Information We Collect Automatically**

Whenever you visit or interact with the Sites, we, as well as any third-party advertisers and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how the Sites are accessed and used (" **Usage Information** "). Usage Information may include, in part, browser type, operating system, the page served, the time, and the preceding page views. This statistical data provides us with information about the use of this Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on this Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they "click" on. This information helps us keep our website fresh and interesting to our visitors and tailor content to a visitor's interests. Usage Information is generally non-identifying.

We also automatically collect your IP address or other unique identifier (" **Device Identifier** ") for the computer, mobile device, technology or other device (collectively, " **Device** ") you use to access the Sites. A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device when you access a website or its servers, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier.

The technologies used on the Sites to collect Usage Information, including Device Identifiers, include:

_**Cookies**._ Cookies are data files placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Sites. We, or our third-party advertising service providers, may place cookies or similar files on your Device for security purposes, to facilitate site navigation and to personalize your experience while visiting the Sites. Cookies allow us to collect technical and navigational information, such as browser type, time spent on our site and pages visited. Cookies allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Site. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. However, please be aware that some features of this Site may not function properly or may be slower if you disable cookies.

_**Web Beacons**. _Small graphic images or other web programming code called web beacons may be included in the Sites and email messages. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Sites, to monitor how users navigate the Sites, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to determine whether content sent was actually viewed.

####  2\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE SITES

Any information you submit on the Sites will be used for a variety of business purposes, including for example, to: respond to your questions and requests; provide you with access to certain areas and features of the Sites; verify your identity; administer your participation in our promotions; communicate with you about your activities on the Sites; tailor content, advertisements, and offers we serve you; improve the Sites and for internal business purposes; contact you with regard to your use of the Sites, your account, and, in our discretion, changes to our policies; and for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your Personal Information or otherwise with your consent.

####  3\. SHARING OF INFORMATION

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not provide any of your Personal Information to any third parties without your specific consent. We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and Usage Information with third parties. We may also share your information as disclosed at the time you provide your information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances:

**Third Parties Providing Services On Our Behalf and Affiliates.** In order to carry out your requests, to make various features, services and materials available to you through this Site, and to respond to your inquiries, we may share your Personal Information with third parties that perform functions on our behalf (or on behalf of our partners), such as companies or individuals that: host or operate our Sites; analyze data; provide customer service; advertisers; sponsors or other third parties that participate in or administer our promotions or provide marketing or promotional assistance (such as in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list). Your personally identifiable information may also be used by us or shared with our subsidiaries, affiliates, sponsors, partners, advertisers or other affiliated parties to provide you with product information and promotional and other offers.

**Your Agreement To Have Your Personal Information Shared.** While on our Sites, you may have the opportunity to opt-in to receive information and/or marketing offers from someone else or to otherwise consent to the sharing of your information with a third party. If you agree to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to the third party and the Personal Information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that third party.

**Business Transfers.** We may share your Personal Information with other entities affiliated with us for internal reasons, primarily for business and operational purposes. As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all or substantially all of our assets, or assets related to this Site, Personal Information, Usage Information, and any other information that we have collected about the users of one or more of the Sites may be disclosed to such entity as part of the due diligence process and will be transferred to such entity as one of the transferred assets. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.

**Legal Disclosure.** We may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, Usage Information and Device Identifier (including IP address), to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce our Terms of Use or other applicable policies; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, visitors to the Sites or the public.

####  4\. INFORMATION WE RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website and you opt-in to receive information from us, that website will forward to us your e-mail address and other information so that we may contact you. You may also choose to participate in a third party application or feature (such as one of our Facebook or Twitter applications or a similar application or feature on a third party web site) through which you allow us to collect (or the third party to share) information about you, including Personal Information. In addition, we may receive information about you if other users of a third party web site give us access to their profiles and you are one of their "connections" or information about you is otherwise accessible through your "connections’" web page, profile page, or similar page on a social networking or other third party website or interactive service.

We may also supplement the information we collect about you through the Sites with outside records from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may combine the information we receive from these third parties with information we collect through the Sites. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any Personal Information received, unless we have disclosed otherwise.

####  5\. YOUR CHOICE AND ACCESS

You may always direct us not to share your Personal Information with third parties, not to use your Personal Information to provide you with information, offers, newsletters, e-mails and other communications by: (i) updating your registration profile preferences on the Site, (ii) sending us an e-mail at our Contact address provided below; (iii) contacting us by mail at our Contact address provided below; or (iv) following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive. Please specify the applicable Sites or brands for which you do not wish to receive communications.  Your opt-out request will be processed within 30 days of the date on which we receive it.

If you wish to verify, correct, or update any of your personal information collected through the Sites, you may edit your registration profile preferences on the Site, where available, or contact us at the below Contact address or e-mail. In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain Personal Information you have submitted through the Sites.  We are under no obligation to store such Personal Information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such Personal Information.  In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons.

####  6\. ADVERTISING/BEHAVIORAL TARGETING; HOW TO OPT-OUT

We may license technology to serve advertisements on the Sites and within the Sites’ content as that content is served across the Internet. In addition, we may use third party network advertisers to serve advertisements and third party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of the Sites and viewing of our content. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personal Information with these third parties, but ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors, and/or analytics service providers may set and access their own cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including Usage Information.

With regard to advertisements, we and our network advertisers may target advertisements for products and services in which you might be interested based on your visits to both the Sites and other websites. Cookies and web beacons, including those set by third party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, or to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. We may share Usage Information about visitors to the Sites with third party advertising companies for the same purposes. We may use a variety of companies to serve advertisements. You may wish to visit: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), which provides information regarding the "opt-out" procedures of certain third party ad servers we may use.

####  7\. CHILDREN

This Site is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. If we determine upon collection that a user is under this age, we will not use or maintain his/her Personal Information without the parent/guardian’s consent. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records. However, in certain circumstances, we may maintain and use such information (in accordance with the rest of this Privacy Policy and applicable law) in order to notify and obtain consent from the parent/guardian and for certain safety, security, liability and other purposes permitted under applicable law. A parent/guardian can review, remove, change or refuse further collection or use of their child’s Personal Information by contacting us as provided above (include child’s name, address and e-mail address).

####  8\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use certain reasonable security measures to help protect your Personal Information. However, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you use the Sites and provide us with your information at your own risk.

####  9\. OTHER SITES

The Sites may contain links to other sites that we do not own or operate. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use our logo(s) as part of a co-branding arrangement. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services or privacy policies or practices. These other sites may send their own cookies to your Device, they may independently collect data or solicit Personal Information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. You should also independently assess the authenticity of any site which appears or claims that it is one of our sites (including those linked to through an email or social networking page).

####  10\. CONSENT TO PROCESSING AND TRANSFER OF INFORMATION

The Sites are operated in the United States, and/or, in the case of certain Sites, Canada. Given that we are an international business, our use of your information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States, Canada and/or other jurisdictions in which our service providers and affiliates may be located. By using the Sites, or providing us with any information, you consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States, Canada and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

####  11\. CHANGES

Please note, we may change information on the Sites and/or this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you. Changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Sites.

####  12\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Attn: Dr Pepper Snapple Group Consumer Relations   
P.O. Box 869077   
Plano, TX 75086-9077   
Re: Privacy Policy (please refer to the applicable site and date of this policy)  
Telephone: 1-800-696-5891  
Email: send us an email
